<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">project-B-Open-Day-Application</string>
    <string name="ExplanationLegend">A legend that explains the floorplan.</string>
    <string name="array_buildingText">Select the building</string>
    <string name="array_floorText">Select the desired floor</string>
    <string name="banner">Banner for each page</string>
    <string name="bericht_contactformulier">Message</string>
    <string name="button_refreshPDF">Refresh PDF</string>
    <string name="card_comm_titl">Communication</string>
    <string name="comm_frag_text1">Organisations are ready for big challenges. Promoting new products, cooperating with clients, colleagues and residents, showing that you do the right things for the society. How do you do that in a period of critical journalism, vloggers, social discussions and constantly new trends? Our course Communication trains you in four years to become a - what we call with pride - a smart connector.</string>
    <string name="comm_frag_text2">A professional who provides smart connections. With help of, for example, social tools, storytelling, big data and co-creation. You develop creative concepts such as mediacampaigns, events and story platforms. Based on proper research, theory and strategy and of course you own creative ideas. You start working with real clients in your first year ranging from entrepreneurs, start-ups, bureaus and national organisations. We work with innovative methods. For example in teams you will use the scrum method where you flexibly and intensively cooperate with you clients.</string>
    <string name="comm_frag_text3">No lesson, course or project is the same. We adapt the working form on the things you learned: webinars. TED Talks, content cafés, meetups, guest tutors and company tours. The course Communication teaches you as a smart connector to touch people, to connect and to move.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_frag_text1">You design meaningful interactive products and services for the people: from websites, apps, interactive installation, to complete experiences. Before you start with your design, you have to perform extensive research to the user’s needs and to the environment where your interactive design will be used.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_frag_text2">You constantly check with the user you make the design for and involve them on location. Designing is nothing more then: making prototypes, testing, failing, redesigning, testing, readjusting and repeat. You will be busy making sketches, researching and building. You learn to work from the perspective of the requirements and experience of the users and clients. An active attitude is a requirement for the design process at Communication and Multimedia Design as well as a healthy portion of curiosity, guts and independency to deliver quality products. Besides that, we expect you to be able to have critical judgement for your own work and work ethics.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_frag_text3">The first-year students now focus on the elderly who experience physical or psychological health problems to a greater or lesser extent and need informal care. The client is looking for smart, new technological applications that the elderly, with the help of informal caregivers, can make living at home longer.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_frag_text4">The CMD course challenges you to use your knowledge, creativity and design talent for interactive products and services that make the life and environment of users more pleasant or even improve.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_gam_frag_text1">As a CMGT person you are a developer (programmer) of interactive digital products: you develop web and mobile applications and you know the basics of developing games. However, the boundaries between these digital products and the physical world are becoming increasingly blurred and faster. You are therefore not trained as a specialist in 1 specific programming language or platform, but as a flexible programmer who can quickly master the possibilities of a new language or platform (smartphone, game console, Internet of Things). With the aim of devising and developing interactive solutions for customers that transcend platform and programming language. You differentiate yourself from other programmers by your level of creativity and your knowledge and sense of interaction between devices and people (users).</string>
    <string name="comm_med_gam_frag_text2">A Rotterdam CMGT person distinguishes himself from other programmers by the degree of creativity and the design-oriented approach and the degree of knowledge and feeling for interaction between devices and people (users). The person who will use it is central to everything you make. That is why you have an inquisitive attitude and you want to get to know users and involve them as intensively as possible in making the product. The activities and possibilities for this creative technologist are subject to change because many developments are taking place in the field. Now the emphasis is on web and mobile technologies. Game technologies form a smaller part.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_gam_frag_text3">CMGT students work with students of the Communication and Multimedia Design course at certain times. This collaboration is important because when developing interactive solutions, collaboration with other creative specialists, such as designers and strategists, leads to higher end quality.</string>
    <string name="comm_med_gam_frag_text4">After this study, CMGT employees start working as programmers at internet agencies or other agencies in the creative sector (advertising, marketing, design, innovation). Some start their own business or start working as a freelancer. Web Developer and Mobile Developer are therefore the professions that many graduates currently practice after completing their studies.</string>
    <string name="comm_media_text">Studying with us often looks different. As a designer you do not sit in the traditional school desks. We work together in the studio for real clients.</string>
    <string name="comm_text">Do you have a keen eye and ear for the stories of people and brands? Are you creative with text and image and fascinated by the world of media? Then the Communication course is for you!</string>
    <string name="contact_informatie">Contact information</string>
    <string name="crea_med_gam_text">Creative technologists invent and develop innovative digital products, where the user is central.</string>
    <string name="datum_od_14feb">14 Februari</string>
    <string name="datum_od_1apr">1 April</string>
    <string name="dinsdag">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="donderdag">Thursday</string>
    <string name="inf_frag_text1">We train you to be a software engineer. You get started with developing software for various applications. You are able to analyze, design and implement complex IT systems.</string>
    <string name="inf_frag_text2">Software can be found all around us. You are the specialist in creating large and complex software information systems that work quickly, efficiently and securely. You can think of developing a functional app, but also analyzing large amounts of data from social media. When developing these systems you come into contact with different programming languages. In the first year you learn how to program in Python and advanced programming languages such as Java / C #. From the second year on, you choose which programming language you want to use. In addition to programming and developing various applications, you also learn to collaborate.</string>
    <string name="inf_frag_text3">After completing the Computer Science course you can be widely deployed within the field. From functions such as data engineer, software developer and software engineer you can grow further within IT.</string>
    <string name="inf_frag_text4">Are you interested in new technological developments, curious, a little quirky and a go-getter, then the Computer Science course is for you!</string>
    <string name="inf_text">We train you to be a software engineer. You get started with developing software for various applications. You are able to analyze, design and implement complex IT systems.</string>
    <string name="informatica_titl">Computer science</string>
    <string name="inft_frag_text1">In daily life we have become increasingly dependent on IT systems. Traveling in public transportation is only possible with the OV chip card, your luggage will automatically arrive at the right place at Schiphol, energy meters will become \"smart\" and medical interventions are sometimes done by a device instead of a surgeon.</string>
    <string name="inft_frag_text2">All examples where hardware and software come together in a single system. As a technical computer scientist you contribute to the development, security and keeping up of these systems. During the study you will become acquainted with the technical aspects of IT. You learn to program in various programming languages, including the so-called \'lower\' languages for hardware applications. With this you learn to develop solutions for different devices, robots and other modern systems.</string>
    <string name="inft_frag_text3">You are an all-rounder in all disciplines, but you also specialize in one or more aspects in the professional field. Think of Machine Learning, Augmented Reality, Automated Systems and of course the with IoT (Internet of Things) closely connected with Embedded Systems.</string>
    <string name="maandag">Monday</string>
    <string name="naam_voor_formulier">Name</string>
    <string name="nav_BuildingPlan">Floorplan</string>
    <string name="nav_ContactForm">Questionform</string>
    <string name="nav_Courses">Courses CMI</string>
    <string name="nav_Dates">Dates Open Days</string>
    <string name="nav_StartScreen">Homescreen</string>
    <string name="onderwerp">Subject</string>
    <string name="openingstijden">opening time</string>
    <string name="routebeschrijving">Route description</string>
    <string name="send_button_description">Send</string>
    <string name="time_friday">7.30 - 17.30</string>
    <string name="time_monday">7.30 - 22.00</string>
    <string name="time_thursday">7.30 - 19.30</string>
    <string name="time_tuesday">7.30 - 21.00</string>
    <string name="time_wednesday">7.30 - 22.00</string>
    <string name="tinf_text">As a technical computer scientist you work on modern IT systems in which hardware and software are integrated. Thanks to your programming and hardware knowledge, you can operate at the intersection thereof.</string>
    <string name="tinf_titl">Technical Informatics</string>
    <string name="titelvragenformulier">Questionform</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Welcome to the HR open day app! Here you can find information about the CMI institute of Hogeschool Rotterdam</string>
    <string name="uitlegvragenformulier">If you have any questions, you can ask them on this page. Enter the details and send your message, we will reach you within 3 working days.</string>
    <string name="vrijdag">Friday</string>
    <string name="warning_tijden">Please note: adjusted opening times may apply during holiday periods.</string>
    <string name="woensdag">Wednesday</string>
</resources>